No radios. You take my telephone.
别用无线电, 带着我的电话
You get anything, you call me through the switchboard.
有任何事, 利用报案中心交换机
Good luck.
祝好运
Thanks. Find that bomb.
谢谢, 去找到那颗炸弹
Ricky, where are they?
瑞奇, 他们在那?
Right over here.
在这边
Senior man present is Chief Allen.
最资深的是艾伦队长
Chief of what?
那个单位?
Transit.
交通
Okay, thanks, Ricky. Gentlemen,
好, 谢谢, 瑞奇
we have a decision to make.
各位, 我们有个决定要下
Chief Allen, the man who has done this has told us that
造成这件事的人说他另外安置了
he has planted another very large bomb in a school here in the New York area.
一个很大的炸弹 就在纽约的某个学校里
And he has told us that we cannot evacuate.
他说我们不能疏散
But he has not said that we cannot search.
但他没说我们不能搜索